<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AusculTech Dx</title>
    <link>at-dx.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AusculTech Dx</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="at-dx.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/privacy/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/privacy/privacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/careers/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/careers/careers/</guid>
      <description>AusculTech Dx is a young, vibrant Digital Health startup rooted in deep science and committed to bringing innovative technology to pediatric medicine.
We have open positions for entrepreneurial engineers who share our values and goals of transforming medicine with novel technology.
If that&amp;rsquo;s you, please get in touch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/contact/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/contact/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you want to set up an on-site evaluation or request more info, send us an email at contact@auscultechdx.com
We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Team</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/team/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/team/team/</guid>
      <description>The team is made of entrepreneurs and inventors who have translated novel technologies from research labs into FDA-cleared products.
 Raj Shekhar, PhD Founder and CTO Raj Shekhar is an inventor of the StethAid™ technology, who has led its research and development since inception together with CMO Robin Doroshow. Dr. Shekhar is also a principal investigator and a professor of radiology and pediatrics at Children’s National Hospital and George Washington University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>My super sweet first blog post!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/news/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/news/news/</guid>
      <description>AusculTech Dx receives STTR Phase I award June 2020 AusculTech Dx received its latest STTR Phase I award from the National Institutes of Health (NIH). This award supports research and development into extending the StethAid™ platform for improved home-based management of childhood asthma.
ACME-POCT selects AusculTech Dx for a seed grant January 2020 A seed grant from Emory/Georgia Tech/Children’s based Atlanta Center for Microsystems Engineered Point-of-Care Technologies (ACME POCT) is enabling AusculTech Dx to research and develop next-generation StethAid™ technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Mission</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/team/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/team/mission/</guid>
      <description>Our goal is to be the leading pediatric cardiopulmonary auscultation platform. By bringing specialist-quality knowledge into primary care offices and homes, our platform empowers providers and parents to give the best care they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/pubs/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/pubs/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Automated Identification of Innocent Still’s Murmur in Children Sukryool Kang, Robin Doroshow, James McConnaughey, Raj Shekhar
A Smartphone Stethoscope and Application for Automated Identification of Innocent Still’s Murmur Titus John, Robin W. Doroshow, Raj Shekhar
Heart Sound Segmentation toward Automated Heart Murmur Classification in Pediatric Patents Sukryool Kang, Robin Doroshow, James McConnaughey, Ahsan Khandoker, Raj Shekhar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology</title>
      <link>at-dx.github.io/tech/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>at-dx.github.io/tech/tech/</guid>
      <description>AusculTech Dx is a Children’s National Hospital spin-off commercializing auscultation-analysis research.
 What is auscultation? Auscultation is the act (or process) of listening to the heart, lung, and other body sounds using a stethoscope as part of a medical exam.
Meet StethAidTM StethAidTM is our digital stethoscope, which along with the mobile app and web dashboard, form our smart digital auscultation platform.
 Streamlined Care StethAidTM brings intelligent heart murmur identification from specialist offices to primary care offices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
